(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T13:14:56.286275",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
But we're striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Been smashing barriers left and right
That's our myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright!
フリュー
FuRyu
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen,
the harbinger of order, leader of justice,
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see ya, to see ya! Lovely!
It's Gigi Murin! It's Gigi Murin!
And today again, you can call me
the beast terror!
And I'm Cecilia Immergreen,
the ancient automaton,
spin twin!
Ciao ragatini!
This is Raora Panthera!
And we are JUSTICE!
Justice, just like that!
Justice, get, get, bust!
Yes, this concert was amazing, right?
But we still have one day left.
I'm so, so excited to see
what the sunfishes have in store for us today.
What about you guys?
Today's performance is going to be
even more hype and exciting! So get ready!
Let's do this!
Everyone! Three! Two! One!
Breaking Dimensions!
Mori Calliope
Takanashi Kiara
Ninomae Ina'nis
Gawr Gura
Watson Amelia
MYTH
IRyS
Ceres Fauna
Ouro Kronii
Nanashi Mumei
Hakos Baelz
PROMISE
Shiori Novella
Koseki Bijou
Nerissa Ravencroft
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Mococo Abyssgard
ADVENT
壁をぶち破れ！
Break the wall!
Are you Ready!?
Are you ready for this? Come on everyone, it's time to break out!
A-D-V-E-N-T
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Spreading out like wildfire
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter
Start the fire
Come pull me out
I'm out of sheep to count
This overkill of sad old stories wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time where yours to discover
This is our time waiting for us to discover
Hello, brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Ignite our beating hearts
Dance into the flame of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Dance until the end of time
異世界の見えない向こう側 貫いて手を挙げる
Piercing through the unseen other side of another world, raising our hands
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
One step to the left
Two steps to the right
Then back to where we started, and then over again
Step out of the circle
Break out, we've got everything
This is our time where yours to discover
This is our time waiting for us to discover
Blue sky, take us home
To where we belong
And free us from the night, take us to paradise
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Ignite our beating hearts
Dance into the flame of life
それぞれの聖地へ
To our respective sacred grounds
Dance until the end of time
奇跡の向こう側 連れてってあげる
Taking you beyond the miracle
I know that I can still be the future of this story
I know that I can be free, the one and only
They tell me that I'm crazy, I'll never let them stop me
With this, our Advent begins!
Time to get this party started!
Never ever, have I ever, been a sinner, been a dreamer
Fire, fire, light the fire
can you hear ? can you hear all our heartbeats
Can you hear? Can you hear all our heartbeats
echo for a brand - new start ?
Echo for a brand-new start?
anytime , anyplace , anyone can join on the fun
Anytime, anyplace, anyone can join on the fun
キラメキ に 乗っ て ( yay )
riding the sparkles (Yay!)
how can i ever forget ? our very first song
How can I ever forget? Our very first song
( a distant memory )
(A distant memory)
my voice was trembling , i still remember it
My voice was trembling, I still remember it
( just a little bit )
(Just a little bit)
our future started that day on , and it 's so bright
Our future started that day on, and it's so bright
we seized the day together , all at once
We seized the day together, all at once
it keeps going on , and on , and on , and on
It keeps going on, and on, and on, and on
my heartbeat getting stronger
( you and me ) we can go there if we want to
(You and me) We can go there if we want to
( are you ready ? ) yeah , we ' re all set , okay
(Are you ready?) Yeah, we're all set, okay
open the doors into our crazy dreams
( one , two , three , キラメキ rider )
(One, two, three, Kirameki Rider)
( ay ay ay ya )
(Ay, ay, ay, ya)
take a dive from the sky into the deepest hell
if you survive down below where the darkness dwells
so deep that you can't even hear the bells
all along was our nest , couldn't even tell
All along was our nest, couldn't even tell.
跋扈 大気 駆け抜ける lightning
Rampaging through the atmosphere, lightning,
唸る 影 旋風 frightening
Howling shadow, whirlwind frightening,
井 の 中 で イキ る ニンゲン に
to you humans living arrogantly in your small well.
actions all have con - sequences
Actions all have consequences,
oh you humans so naive and desperate
enough to think that luck and fate have favorites
禁忌 を 感じ たい の なら 触れ
If you want to feel the taboo, touch it,
抗 って その 運命
defy that destiny!
oh oh oh oh
if you reach for it i 'll burn ya with a dragon 's heart of fire
If you reach for it, I'll burn ya with a dragon's heart of fire!
跪け 従い な
Kneel and obey!
ay ay ay ya
flying straight into desire
ever oh so higher
空 全て 支配 下
The entire sky is under my control.
ay ay ay ya
それでも 抗う ？ 掛かってこい
Still want to defy me? Come at me!
屈服 or conquer me 逆鱗
Submit or conquer me, Gekirin!
( ay ay ay ya )
(Ay, ay, ay, ya)
ring it ring it gekirin
龍神 に make it ring
Make it ring for the Dragon God!
bring it bring it gekirin
if you wanna be the king
ring it ring it gekirin
龍神 に make it ring
Make it ring for the Dragon God!
bring it bring it gekirin
if you wanna be the king
もう 待て ない か ？ my awakening
Can't you wait anymore? My awakening,
so strange that you can't stop shivering
陶酔 したい んだ ろ 聖火 に
You want to be intoxicated by the holy fire,
awww you 're climbing up my body 龍 の 巣 の 番人
aww, you're climbing up my body, guardian of the dragon's nest.
hey 盗ん で みな wake me up
Hey, try to steal it and wake me up,
baby 足 の 置き場 せいぜい 気付け な
baby, watch your step and take heed.
キス して 誓い は 永遠 の ラヴァー
Kiss me, the vow is an eternal lover,
消え ない その mark , a cursed power
that unfading mark, a cursed power.
禁忌 を 感じ たい の なら 触れ
If you want to feel the taboo, touch it,
抗 って その 運命
defy that destiny!
oh oh oh oh
地獄 の 業火 呑り 飲み な
swallow the hellfire,
干上がら せ て やる この 大河
I'll dry up this great river.
chaos on pangaea
ay ay ay ya
天 に まで 昇り たい か
do you want to ascend all the way to heaven?
祝福 or get your 対価
Blessing or get your price!
take off from the tip of the spire
ay ay ay ya
if you really wanna win and take ev ' rything
If you really wanna win and take everything,
look with in , and begin
look within and begin,
逆鱗
Gekirin!
you'll feel a burning wrath that makes the heart freeze
you'll face creatures from a deep far off sea
you'll face creatures from a deep far-off sea,
your faith will grow like longan fruit from the seed
纏う この 神威
Clothed in this divine majesty,
oh oh oh oh
きこう その 願い
hear that wish.
oh oh oh oh
if you reach for it i 'll burn ya with a dragon 's heart of fire
If you reach for it, I'll burn ya with a dragon's heart of fire!
跪け 従い な
Kneel and obey!
ay ay ay ya
flying straight into desire
ever oh so higher
空 全て 支配 下
The entire sky is under my control.
ay ay ay ya
それでも 抗う ？ 掛かってこい
Still want to defy me? Come at me!
屈服 or conquer me 逆鱗
Submit or conquer me, Gekirin!
( ay ay ay ya )
(Ay, ay, ay, ya)
ring it ring it gekirin
龍神 に make it ring
Make it ring for the Dragon God!
bring it bring it gekirin
if you wanna be the king
ring it ring it gekirin
龍神 に make it ring
Make it ring for the Dragon God!
bring it bring it gekirin
if you got it , you'll be king
If you got it, you'll be king!
(もぐもぐ)
(Mogu Mogu)
森羅万象の悪戦苦闘も
Even the hardest thing in all the world
マヨネーズかけたら大体美味しくなる?
If you put mayonnaise on it, it tastes good!
君が泣いてもお腹は空くよ
Even if you cry, you'll still get hungry.
消化できなかったごめんごめん。
Couldn't digest it, sorry, sorry.
酸いも甘いも勝手に食べて
Sour things, sweet things, I'll eat 'em all I want!
ご迷惑おかけしています
Very sorry to trouble you so.
パクチーな生　変な味のジュース
Cilantro arrangement, weird flavored juice,
心を無にして飲み込みます
ignoring my heart, I gulp it down.
ああ混沌情報過多のレストランで
Ah, chaotic information overload at the restaurant.
もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu...
銃撃戦の真ん中でもぐもぐ
Right in the middle of a firefight, mogu mogu!
満腹になる未来を願っているよ
I'm hoping for a future where I'm full.
もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu...
世界が終わる前に
Before the world ends...
もぐもぐやみィマジ神
Mogu mogu, yummy, godlike crazy!
むにゃむにゃありのまんなま
Yum yum, frankly munching, munching.
もぐもぐやみィ magic coming
Mogu mogu, yummy, magic coming!
この世を味わうんだうまうま
Tasting this world, yum yum!
理論武装のミルフィーユサンド
Theoretically backed mille-feuille sandwich,
匿名希望のオーロラソース
Wishing to be anonymous aurora source.
大雑把な味付け多目に見とよ
Roughly seasoned, but overlook it.
美味しくなったら「おっおっ。」
If it's tasty, it's ok, ok!
良いモン悪いモンいっぱい食べて汚れた口拭ぬぐいます
Good things, bad things, eat lots and I'll wipe my dirty mouth.
おにぎりピザケーキ豪華なフルコース罠を疑い気をつけます
Extravagant full course meal, question if it's a trap and be careful.
ああ妄想流言飛語のバイキングで
Wild ideas, groundless rumors of a buffet,
もぐもぐ
mogu mogu...
デスゲームの教室でもぐもぐ
In a death game classroom, mogu mogu!
仲の良い君と生き残れたらいいな
It'd be nice if you, my good friend, would survive.
もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu...
数年後もこの場所で
In a few years at this place...
もぐもぐやみィマジ神
Mogu mogu, yummy, godlike crazy!
今夜の晩ごはんは
Tonight's dinner will be...
もぐもぐやみィ magic coming
Mogu mogu, yummy, magic coming!
次はのお前の番だ
Next time will be your turn!
もぐもぐやみィマジ神
Mogu mogu, yummy, godlike crazy!
むにゃむにゃありのまんなま
Yum yum, frankly munching, munching.
もぐもぐやみィ magic coming
Mogu mogu, yummy, magic coming!
この世を味わうんだうまうま
Tasting this world, yum yum!
もぐもぐまいぎ yummy
Mogu mogu yummy, yummy...
Mogu mogu yummy, yummy!
Hi, everyone!
Hello, New York!
Second Day, huh?
How are you doing tonight, New York?
Are you guys having a great time?
Yeah! How's the concert so far?
Do you like Rebellion?
Oh, I don't think that was loud enough.
Yo, more please!
Yeah, can't you?
It's our first time as Advent performing together.
Come on, did you like it?
You're gonna break my ears.
That's what I thought.
Yeah!
Well, I guess we should do some introductions first, maybe?
Yeah, like who are you and who am I?
I'm not really sure anymore, honestly.
Me neither.
Well, why don't you go first?
All right.
Shiori!
Shiori Novella here at your service.
Hololive's archivist.
And who might you be, pretty lady?
Hiya, darlings.
This is Hololive English Advent's vocal diva,
the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft.
Thank you for having us here tonight, New York!
Yeah, let's make some noise tonight!
Oh, yes, that's music to my ears.
Honestly, same.
This venue, can we just take a moment to appreciate it?
Yeah. It's gorgeous!
It looks also kind of haunted.
Yeah, it does look a little bit haunted.
What do you think we should do with it?
We should summon a ghost.
You I mean, I'm already a demon, so...
I'll summon a prettier ghost.
You said you're a demon!
Oh, my heart!
You just killed me in front of everybody!
Should I get him up to you?
Here, here, here.
Just just turn her...
Okay, I know what to do.
Okay.
I got your nose!
I can't breathe!
Help me!
I got your nose.
Give it back?
Okay, here you go.
Thank you.
Woah.
We wanted to do some call and responses with you guys, if that's okay.
So how I like to summon goes is by being like really annoying, so I think we should recite the lyrics, right?
Yes, so we're gonna say "fire, fire" and then right after, you're gonna say "light the fire".
Got it, everyone?
That's supposed to make ghosts come out!
All right.
One, two, three.
Fire! Fire!
I don't think that's loud enough.
Let's do one more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Count down.
One, two, three.
Fire! Fire!
That's loud!
I can feel the spirits.
Um, I want to do one more actually, selfishly of me.
It's not really a call and response, but I just want the audience for, for me, for myself.
I just want to hear you all say "ope".
I'm going to do a countdown, can you all just say "ope" for me?
Well, but, but can you tell us the origin of "ope"? Like a really quick summary.
Ope is just a an expression, like "ope" of surprise.
Ope!
You don't have to sound surprised, you can just say "ope" though.
Okay, on three.
I won't make you do it twice, so you got one try.
Can you get it for me?
Watch out.
Okay, okay.
One, two, three.
Ope!
Well, you know, we're here for breaking dimensions.
Yeah.
We should talk about what, what does breaking dimensions mean?
To me, to you?
Me? Somebody go.
Well, well, what breaking dimension means to me...
I feel like it's a physical achievement because this is our first concert.
Yeah, really, and I kind of feel the same.
It's like, I feel like this is solidifying our existence, being here, right?
Yeah, like, you know, we've been in Hololive for about a year,
but now it feels really, really official, standing before you, seeing you guys out in the audience, up there and online too.
Yeah.
Hi, guys.
Hey, I'm walking here.
Haha.
Yeah, move it, I'm walking here.
Well, it's, it's really great to be here because, like, it feels, feels so real, right?
Yeah, it really does feel real.
It's real.
You guys, it's like I could touch you.
The accident wasn't my fault.
Me, I'm so happy to be here with all of Advent, but especially with my...
Well, love each other, will we?
Is it a ghost?
Okay, okay, I got you, I got you in the neck.
Who's a good girl?
Who's my little paw gem?
Who's my bag gem?
What's wrong with you?
I don't know, there's a lot.
Hey, I, same, honestly.
That's cool.
Well, we're having a great time.
Uh, we do have some potentially maybe bad news...
...which is if you are at this point of the concert watching online, uh, this is where the free portion of the show ends.
That's right!
No more sneak peeks! No more sneaking and no more peeking in that order!
Yep, so if you're going to want to watch the rest of the concert and you're online, be sure to head over to SPWN and you can get a ticket...
...and watch the rest of the concert if you want to see uh my solo performance today as well as everybody else's amazing performances.
There's going to be so many wonderful songs! So that's right!
Get your purchases! Let's go!
I should, should we do the thing?
Oh, that's right.
All right, let's fuse.
Okay, everyone...
I hope you enjoy Breaking Dimensions!
look up at the horizon
together as one
a star is on the rise
and it's only begun
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.